Guide to the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South Records, 1939-2018 RL.01081
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Series, 1974-1990 and undated
  - Case 3
    - 1989, Apr. 7-8:Women, Faith, and Housing Conference: Workshop, Don Sanders (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - 1989, Apr. 7-8:Women, Faith, and Housing Conference: Worship (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - 1989, Apr. 7-8:Women, Faith, and Housing Conference: Closing (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - 1989, May:Katie Cannon (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - 1989, Oct. 1:Jeanette Stokes, sermon, Church of Reconciliation, Chapel Hill, N.C. (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - 1990, May 27-29:Carter Heyward and Katie Cannon, Women in Ministry, N.C. Conference (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - 1991, May:Mary Hunt, Women in Ministry, N.C. Conference: Women, Sexuality, and Spirituality, Browns Summit, N.C., (Located in audiocassete Case 4) (Folder 38a-b)
      - Sessions I-II (Box 10, Folder 38a)
      - Sessions II-III (Box 10, Folder 38b)
    - undated:"Answer to Homelessness in Housing" workshop (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Case 4
    - undated:"Bread and Roses" (with filmstrip), (See kit folders) (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - undated:K. Gonzales, "Why Should the Church Support Equal Rights For Women?" (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - undated:Jean Houston, author, "The Possible Human", interview by Michael Toms (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - undated:Pomegranate Rose, "As We Are," (See kit folders) (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - undated:Peggy Way (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - undated:"Women of Faith" Tape 1, (See kit folder) (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - undated:"Women of Faith" Tape 2 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - undated:"Women of Faith" Tape 3 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - undated:"Women of Faith" Tape 4 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Dr. Amata Miller "Biblical Reflection," 1983, Dec. 9,(Videocassette) (Box 10)
    - Dr. Amata Miller "Economic Literacy," 1983, Dec. 9,(2 Videocassettes) (Box 10)
    - Mary Hunt, Women in Ministry, NC Conference: Women, Sexuality, and Spirituality, Browns Summit, N.C, 1991, May (Box 10, Folder 38a-b)
  - Case 5
    - Women, Faith and Economic Justice, 1984, Nov. 16-17 (Box 10, Folder 15a-e)
- Pictures Series, 1983-1989, undated
  Primarily consists of 3"x5" color photographs of participants at various conferences organized by the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South. Also included are black and white photographs and negatives. The first part of the series is arranged chronologically, the rest alphabetically by conference name.
  - 1986, April 23 (Box 10)
  - 1989, Oct., undated, 3 folders (Box 10)
  - "Can We Be Different But Not Alienated?" Conference, Browns Summit, N.C., 1989, May 14-16 (Box 10)
  - "Keeping Yourself Together While Changing the World" Conference, Greensboro, N.C., 1987, Sept. 19-20 (Box 10)
  - "Telling Our Stories: Women, Language, and Spiritual Journey" Conference, Browns Summit, N.C., 1988, May 29-31 (Box 10)
  - "Women, Faith, and Economic Justice" Conference:
    - Durham, N.C., 1984, Nov. 16-17 (Box 10)
    - Greensboro, N.C., 1985, Nov. 15-16 and 1990, March 30-31 (Box 10)
    - Raleigh, N.C., 1987, Mar. 25-26 (Box 10)
  - "Women, Faith, and Economic Justice" Conference, 1992 (Box 10)
  - "Women, Faith, and Health Care Justice" Conference, Greensboro, N.C., 1988, Mar. 25-26 (Box 10)
  - "Women, Faith, and Housing" Conference, Durham, N.C., 1989, Apr. 7-8 (Box 10)
  - "Women, Faith, and Tax Justice" Conference, with Teresa Amett, undated (Box 10)
  - "Women in Ministry in North Carolina" Conference: Asheboro, N.C., 1983, May 17-19, Browns Summit, N.C., 1986, May 11-13; 1987, May 31-June 2 (Box 10)
  - "Women in Ministry in North Carolina" Conference: The art of feeding the Spirit, 1990, May (Box 10)
  - "Women in Ministry in North Carolina" Conference: Women, Sexuality, and Spirituality, Mary Hunt, Browns Summit, N.C., 1991, May (Box 10)
  - "Women in Ministry in North Carolina" Conference: Keeping Yourself Together, 1992 (Box 10)
  - "Women in Ministry in the Virginias" Conference: Roanoke, Va., 1986, Oct. 19-21; 1987, Oct. 18-20; 1988, Oct. 16-18 (Box 10)
  - "Women in Ministry in the Virginias" Conference [Kerr Lake, Va.] Phyllis Trible, undated (Box 10)
  - Workshop with Card and Bren at Avalon in Greensboro, n.d (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous: Smith, Christine, "Women in Ministry in the Virginias" Conference, 1991 (Box 10)
- Miscellaneous Series, 1983-1992
  Includes subscriptions to South of the Garden, correspondence concerning the formation and incorporation of the Resource Center for Women and Ministry in the South, and timelines and other documents pertaining to the history of the Resource Center. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Books, catalogs, 1983-1988 (Box 11)
  - Books: Publishing House Publicity Directors (Box 11)
  - Job descriptions, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
  - Mailing lists, Publications subscriptions, etc., 1988-1990, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Resource Center:
    - Attorney, 1977-1985 (Box 11)
    - History, 1977-1992 (Box 11)
- Oversize Materials
  - Alphabetical Files, 1977-1990, undated (Oversize-folder OC:III:1)
  - Financial Papers, 1983-1989 (Oversize-folder OC:III:1)
  - Meetings, Conferences, and Workshops, 1980-1984 (Oversize-folder OC:III:1)
  - Printed Material, 1981 and 1987 (Oversize-folder OC:III:1)
- Addition (1994-0083), 1980-1992, 1 Box and additional oversize material
  Partially processed addition (1994-083) (850 items; dated 1980-1992) comprises files pertaining to the Guilford Women's Network and miscellaneous conference, financial, and meeting files.
  - Files (Box Acc. 94/083: Box 1)
  - Files (Oversize-box Acc. 94/083: OC.III.I)
- Additions (1995-0035), (1995-0082), and (1997-0114), 1980-1990s, 10 boxes
  Partially processed additions (1995-035, 1995-082, 1997-114) (4000 items, dated 1980-[199-]) contain administrative files including those for Center-related projects such as the Women's Economic Justice Conference, the Women and Violence Conference, and the Body and Soul retreat, all in 1993, as well as the N.C. Workplace Reform Mission in 1994. There are other conference, workshop, financial, and meeting files, and various publications of the Center.
  - Files (Box Acc. 95/035: Box 1-2)
  - Files (Box Acc. 95/082: Box 1)
  - Files (Box Acc. 97/114: Box 1-7)
- Addition (1999-0314), 1980s-1990s; 1.2 Linear Feet 2 boxes; 1 oversize folder
  Scope and Contents
  Addition (1999-0314) contains papers of Women In Ministry of NC; files related to Women Clergy/Professional Developers Re-Imagining Conversation; and event planning and programming files.
  - Files (Box Acc. 99/314: Box 1-2)
  - Files (Oversize-folder Acc. 99/314: Folder 1)
- Addition (2003-0240), 1987-2003, 2 Boxes and 1 Oversize Folder
  Addition (2003-240) (300 items, 0.8 lin. ft.; dated 1987-2003) contains files of RCWMS founder Jeanette Stokes; subject files; correspondence; writings and speeches; and publication files. Includes flyers, brochures, invitations, newsletters, and artifacts (political buttons and a banner).
  - Files (Box Acc. 03/240: Box 1-2)
  - Files (Box Acc. 03/240: OC:VII:9)
- Addition (2004-0151), 1991-1999, 5 boxes
  Addition (2004-151) (1650 items, 2.6 lin. ft.; dated 1991-1999) consists primarily of files associated with events organized by the RCWMS; newsletter files; subject files; and research files. Includes drafts, correspondence, writings, reports, planning documents, schedules, printed material, and other administrative material.
  - Files (Box Acc. 04/151: Box 1-5)
- Addition (2005-0018), 1998-2003, 2 boxes
  Addition (2005-018) (750 items, 1.2 lin. ft.; dated 1998-2003) consists of financial records; meeting minutes, files, interviews, and notes of the North Carolina Council of Churches Task Group on the Effects of the Women's Movement on North Carolina Congregations. Also includes files on equal rights, violence against women, The Spirit Project, and the Reader's Theatre.
  - Files (Box Acc. 05/018: Box 1-2)
- Addition (2006-0115), 1980s, 4 boxes
  Addition (2006-115) (1500 items, 2.0 lin. ft.) includes newsletters, fundraising materials, financial records, reference materials for classes taught by Jeannette Stokes and catalogs. There is also correspondence, business records, schedules, agendas and promotional materials about conferences, workshops and other events. In addition there are 1982 clippings and ephemera about the Equal Rights Amendment and 4 audiocassettes recordings of interviews and sermons.
  - Files (Box Acc. 06/115: Box 1-4)
  - Files (Box Acc. 06/115: Ovsz Folder 1)
- Addition (2007-0019), 1990-2003, 3 boxes
  Addition (2007-0019) (762 items, 1.5 lin. ft.; dated 1990-2003) contains financial files; materials for classes, events, and workshops; one T-shirt and eleven audio cassettes.
  - Materials for classes, events, workshops, 2002-2003. (Box Acc. 07/019: Box 1)
  - Financial files, 1990-1998 (Box Acc. 07/019: Box 2)
  - Materials for classes, events and workshops, 2003 (Box Acc. 07/019: Box 2)
  - Promotional materials for a benefit concert for Lise Uyanik and Mobile City Band (Box Acc. 07/019: Box 2)
  - T-shirt (Box Acc. 07/019: Box 3)
  - 11 audio cassettes (Box Acc. 07/019: Box 3)
- Addition (2007-0119), 1997-2007, 2 boxes
  Addition (2007-0119) (1575 items, 2.1 lin. ft.; dated 1997-2007) contains program and workshop files; correspondence; drafts and materials relating to God Speaks, Women Respond; and administrative materials.
  - 25th Anniversary, 2002 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Jeannette Stokes and Mary Margarent Wade (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Resource Center logbook, 1997-2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Calendar printouts, 2004-2007 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - General Assembly, June 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Duke Youth Assembly (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Beach, June 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Amy Kellum, June 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Women over 60, April 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Writing Week, May 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Binkley Women, April-May 2004, 2 folders (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Lectures at Wake, March 2, 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Deer in the Meadow/Peacehill, February 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - At Duke Chapel, February 2007 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Same Sex Marriage, February 5, 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Remaking the Labyrinth, 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Menopause, January 24, 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - God Speaks, Women Respond, 7 folders (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - God Speaks, Women Respond, bound copy (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - God Speaks, Women Respond, binder draft (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Book sales (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Afghan: Women (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Carpenter internet AOL (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - AIDS (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Feminist Theologins Network (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Meinrad, August 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Writing Week, August 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Bookmaking, 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - MA 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 1)
  - Evans, Mary CD (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 2)
  - Solstice (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 2)
  - Fund for Southern Communities (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 2)
  - Interfaith, December 5, 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 2)
  - Brigit, January 2005, 2 folders (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 2)
  - Silent Beach, December 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 2)
  - Elaine Neil Orr, November 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 2)
  - NC Center NP, November 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 2)
  - Writers Workshop, October 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 2)
  - Shelley Wiley Pamphlet (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 2)
  - Meinrad, October 2004 (Box Acc. 07/119: Box 2)
- Addition (2007-0151), 2002-2007, 1 boxes
  Addition (2007-0151) (800 items, 1.5 lin. ft.; dated 2002-2007) contains promotional materials; South of the Garden issues; Art and the Feminine Divine exhibit memorabilia and artist applications; and materials relating to the publication of 25 Years in the Garden.
  - Promotional materials (Box Acc. 07/151: Box 1)
  - South of the Garden, 2006-2007 (Box Acc. 07/151: Box 1)
  - Art and the Feminine Divine exhibit memorabilia (Box Acc. 07/151: Box 1)
  - Art and the Feminine Divine artist applications (alphabetically) (Box Acc. 07/151: Box 1)
  - 25 Years in the Garden publication material, 2002 (Box Acc. 07/151: Box 1)
- Addition (2008-0252), 1990s-2008, 3 boxes
  Addition (2008-0252) (1350 items, 1.8 lin. ft; dated 1990s-2008) contains conference materials, correspondence, flyers, and handouts from various workshops dealing with women and economic issues. Also includes copies of South of the Garden. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
  - Socially responsible investing (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - SRI Brochure and followup (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - CED (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - Harvard Divinity School information (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - Journal of Women and Religion, Volume 13 (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - Economic Justice (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - Correspondence (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - Older women (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - International project (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - Pendants (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - Advertising and Announcements (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - Publishing Ideas, 2004 (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - Creativity and Spirituality, 1997 (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - South of the Garden newsletters, 2006-2008 (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 1)
  - Economic Justice and Poverty files (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 2)
  - Women labor files (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 2)
  - Economic Justice Conferences (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 2)
  - State CED Roundtable, 1991-1992 (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 2)
  - CCSH/Self Help Background (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 2)
  - Women's Employment Issues files (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 2)
  - Women and Economic Justice resource binder (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 3)
  - Ecumenical Decade (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 3)
  - Women Fighting Poverty (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 3)
  - Presbyterian Women United for Economic Justice (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 3)
  - El Paso, 1992 (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 3)
  - Economic Justice, Religious Language (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 3)
  - The Church and Global Economy report (Box Acc. 08/252: Box 3)
- Accession (2009-0219), 2005-2009, 2 boxes
  Addition (2009-0219) (900 items; 1.2 lin. ft.; dated 2005-2009) includes Art and the Feminine Devine materials, name files of artists, other administrative files for conferences and office activities, and some publications, including South of the Garden.
  Arrangement note
  Materials arrived with labeled folders, which have been transcribed here to increase access for researchers. Files have not been processed, and titles have not been checked for accuracy at this time.
  - AFD in Raleigh, Fall 2006 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Budget-AFD (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Art & Fem. Divine (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Feb 2006 Meeting to pick cont for AFD (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Workshops-Planning (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Artists-Art Fem. Div. (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Packet to Artists (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Call-Mailing Fall AFD (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Press Release (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Postcard (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Joyce (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Sallye Coyle (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - AFD Artist Images for Publicity (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Dawn-Durham Paper (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - AFD-Calendars (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Call for Work AFD (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Description (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Art & Fem. Div Place (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Place: Smaller Venues (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - AFD in Raleigh Long View Gallery (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - AFD Art Sales (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Art Pick up (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Opening-AFD, April 2005 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Venue Notebooks (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Labels (AFD) & Charts (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Contact Artists/Venues Assigned (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - AFD Installation (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - AFD-Drop off (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - 117 Market Street (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - 117 Market-Lease (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Blayloc Cafe (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Francesca's (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Okon/Stern Loft AFD (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 1)
  - Tickets for Ap. 29 Lise U & Stella (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Music AFD GE, Liz, Singin Sistahs, Stella, Lise U (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Jewelsay (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Storytellers (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Art Fem. Divine-Music Kathleen H. (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - AFD-Performers Not Using (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Workshops-In Process (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Cynthia Aldrich (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Heather Crammer AFD (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Martha Dyer & Jan Worther, Feb 2006 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Dana Denniston (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Dori De Stantos/formerly Wilson (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Joanna Haymore (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Peg Gignoux, Dec. 9, 2005 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Ginny Going (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Sandy Milroy (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Owen, Carol (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Ebeth Scott-Sinclair (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Sherri Wood (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Request for number-Artists Art Fem. Div. (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Jennie Malcom (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Beach '05, June 10-12, 2005 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Writing Week, May 2005 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Jude Spacks, May 25, 2005 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Women over 60 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Smith/Buddhism, Ap 7-10 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Margie; Class, March 30, 2005 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Holy Week Labyrinth, March 20-25, 2005 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Duke - Pathways Program, March 8, 2005 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Oct. 27 Feminist Generations Duke (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Writing Week and Tara Retreat, Oct 2005 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - MAOS-Sept 8-11, 2005 Buddhist Meditation (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Women over 60 Writing Group (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Tara Retreat, Oct 7-9, 2005 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - P. Trible Lectures, March 1-2 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Duke, Feb. 8, 2005 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Jan. 2005-10 days Writing Week at Trinity (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Email Calendars, 9/08-7/09 (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
  - Publications (Box Acc. 09/219: Box 2)
- Accession (2010-0166), 2003-2010, 2 boxes
  Includes workshop and retreat files, website mock-ups, Writer's Project grant materials, and the Embrace the Child financial campaign.
  Materials arrived with labeled folders, which have been transcribed here to increase access for researchers. Files have been arranged by date.
  - Requests for Support: The Writer's Project, 2003-2004 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Website mockup/drafts, 2005 (2 folders) (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Writing grant requests, 2005 (2 folders) (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Marie Summers, 2005 Sept 24 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Natural Mandalas, Bree-Kalb, 2005 Sept/Oct (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Calling Forth Kali, Mary Love May and Anita McLeod, 2005 Nov 12 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Sounds of Silence, 2004 Dec 2-4 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Interfaith, 2005 Dec (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Bryant Holsenbeck, 2006 Jan (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Writing Week, 2006 Jan 8-15 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Grounding our Art-Heart, Ann S. Ehringhaus, 2006 Jan 14 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Brigit Day, Mary Love May, 2006 Jan 28 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Art and the Feminine, Melissa York, 2006 Jan 21-Feb 6 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Carrie Newcoming Writing Workshop, 2006 Feb 10-12 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Phyllis Trible lecture, 2006 Feb 28-Mar 1 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Duke Chapel labyrinth, 2006 Mar 7 (2 folders) (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Peace Hill Quiet Day, 2006 Mar 17 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Being Visible, Being Sacred, Being Goddess, Janice Geller and Libby Outlaw, 2006 Mar 18 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Sacred Images, Altars, and Rituals, Adele Wayman, 2006 Mar 25 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Women Over 60 retreat, 2006 Mar 30-Apr 2 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 1)
  - Spring Forward, 2006 Apr 1 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Binkley labyrinth, 2006 Apr 9-14 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - North Carolina Powwow, 2006 Apr (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Moons, Mirrors, and Sacred Fabric Arts, Jude Spacks, 2006 May 3 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Beach retreat, 2006 Jun 9-11 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Writing Week, 2006 Jun 11-18 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Boone, North Carolina, 2006 Oct 4-6 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Women Over 60 (cancelled), 2006 Oct 27-29 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Roanoke, Virginia, 2006 Nov 11 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Interfaith, 2006 Dec (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Advent reflection, 2006 Dec (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Refunds, 2006 Dec (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Embrace the Child, Sally Patton, 2005-2007 (3 folders) (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
  - Email calendars, 2009-2010 (Box Acc. 10/166: Box 2)
- Accession (2011-0146), 2007-2011, 3 boxes
  Accession predominately consists of registration information and handouts from events.
  - Events (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Writing Week, 2007 Jan. 5-12 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Duke PathWays, 2007 Jan. 22 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Women Over 60, 2007 Feb. (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Phyllis Trible Lecture Series: Women and Words, 2007 Mar. 6-7 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - The Labyrinth: A Walking Meditation for Women of All Faiths, 2007 Mar. 8 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Lent, 2007 Mar. 14 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Duke Community Berevement Services Talk, 2007 Mar. 20 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Labyrinth at Duke, 2007 Mar. 27 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Women Over 60, 2007 Mar. 29-Apr. 1 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Labyrinth at Binkley Baptist Church, 2007 Apr. 1-6 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Sharon Doubiago, 2007 Apr. 20-21 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Duke Divinity Women's Week, 2007 Apr. 9-13 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Women and the Prophetic Voice with Carolyn J. Sharp, 2007 Apr. 28 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Pelican House, 1007 Apr. 13-16 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Writing Week, 2007 Apr. 29-May 6 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Beach Retreat, 2007 Jun. 8-10 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Tara Card Invite, 2007 Sept. (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Marie Fortune, 2007 Sept. 4 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - 30th RCWMS Anniversary at Duke Library, 2007 Sept. 6 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Enough Room Party, 2007 Sept. 9 and Oct. 30 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Meditation with Therese Fitzgerald, 2007 Sept. 13-16 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Writing Retreat, 2007 Sept 23-30 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Wise Choices: Women Over 50, 2007 Oct. 4-7 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Wise Choices: Women Over 50 Post Card (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Women Giver, 2007 Oct. 15 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 1)
    - Sallie Bingham Center Symposium, 2007 Oct. 26-27 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Interfaith, 2007 Dec. (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Sounds of Silence, 2007 Nov. 30-Dec. 2 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Writing Week, 2008 Jan. 4-11 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Women Over 60, 2008 Feb. 9 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Holy Ground Layrinth, 2008 Feb. 27 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Phyllis Trible Lecture Series: Interfaith Feminisms, 2008 Mar. 4-5 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Menopause, 2008 Mar. 15 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Labyrinth at Binkley Baptist Church, 2008 Mar. 126-21 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Meggan Moorehead and Film, 2008 Apr. 6 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Virginia Tech Memorial Lie-In, 2008 Apr. 16 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Wise Choices: 2008 Apr. 17-20 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)
    - Conversation with Meinrad Craighead, 2008 Apr. 26 (Box Acc. 11/146: Box 2)